theync.com 2005-12-31

# Privacy Statement

Young Nationalist Corp. and S&S Nationwide Services Inc. which operates the Internet site located at [http://www.youngnationalist.com](http://www.youngnationalist.com/) recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of personally identifiable information collected from visitors to our sites and our subscribers. **Young Nationalist Corp. does not release any information on our users or subscriber to any third party under any circumstances.** No identifiable information is automatically collected from visitors to our Websites. We may collect certain non-personal information to optimize our Web pages for your use. We may use such non-personal information for internal purposes, including but not limited to improving the content of our sites.

Young Nationalist Corp. has created these Websites for your personal information and education. However, you are only authorized to access this Website or to use the materials contained in the Site if you agree to abide by all applicable laws, and our Subscriber/User Disclaimer, which constitutes an Agreement between you and Young Nationalist Corp. Young Nationalist Corp. reserves the right to modify or amend this Agreement without notice at any time. [Click here to send](http://www.youngnationalist.com/contact.htm) any questions or comments regarding, or problems with, this Website.

**REPRINT AND FORWARD POLICY:** We endeavor to advance a worldview based on timeless conservative principles. We don't claim to own them! Thus, subscribers may reprint or forward YoungNationalist.com, in whole or part, with appropriate citation ["The Young Nationalist" and/or "(Young Nationalist Corp.)"] in accordance with "fair use" rules and our Subscriber/User Disclaimer.
